Guide to the Office of Marketing and Communication records ARCH115
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
Office of Marketing and Communication records
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
University of Hartford. Office of Marketing and Communication
ARCH115
10.5 Linear Feet
This collection contains subject records and materials generated by the Office of Marketing and Communications at the University of Hartford.
Box 1-8
Box 9-16
Box 17-21
Conditions Governing Access
The majority of the collection is open to all researchers. Some files are restricted to Office of Communication Staff only. Restricted folders are clearly labelled and noted at the file level in the finding aid.
Existence and Location of Copies
A portion of the collection has been digitized and can be accessed at: http://mdid3.hartford.edu. Access to the digital repository is limited to the University of Hartford Campus. Computers are available to the public at the Harrison Libraries.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains reference files on individuals and topics associated with the University of Hartford.
Related Materials
Office of Communication Development, Marketing, and Publicity Collections
Arrangement
The collection is arranged by accession.
University of Hartford. Office of Marketing and Communication; University of Hartford
- Acc. I. Unknown (People Photographs), 14.21 Linear Feet (35 containers)
  Biographical / Historical
  Before the days of digital images the University kept extensive photo files of individuals for use in University publications and for press releases. Most individuals connected with the University had formal portraits taken from time to time for these purposes. Most of these images were sent to the archives by the Office of Communications after 2006.
  Scope and Contents
  The collection consists primarily of portrait photos and some additional informal shots and snapshots. Although most photographs in the collection are of individuals formally associated with the University, the collection also contains photographs of visiting speakers and performers.
  Related Materials
  The archives contain a number of photograph collections. Additional photographs of individuals may be found within those collections. The document collections in the archives also contain some photographs.
  Arrangement
  The accession is arranged alphabetically by name.
  - A (Box A)
    Includes:
    ?A. R. Kane
    ?Abbe, George
    ?Abrams, Jonathan
    Aaron, Richard
    Abraham, Henry
    Abrahamson, David
    Abrahms, Eliot
    Abrahms, John
    Abrahms, Marc
    Abrahms, Phyllis
    Abrams, Bernard
    Abrams, Bernard/Newspaper clippings
    Abzug, Bella
    Adachi, Natsuko,
    ?Adam, Margie
    Adams, Charles
    Adams, Frederick
    ?Adaskin String Quartet
    Addley, John
    Addley, John/newspaper clippings
    Adleman, Robert
    Adyemi, B.A.
    Aegerter, Pierre
    Ahlquist, Russell
    Ajaye, Franklin
    Alain and Noack
    Albers, Josef
    Alcorn, H. Meade
    Alcorn, Janet
    Aliosi, Jennifer
    Aliosi, Ralph
    Aliota, Jilda
    Aliotta, Jilda
    All the Vales
    Allen, Mildred
    Allen, Richard
    Allened, Don
    Alsing, Carl with Raymond Kasevich
    Alsop, Joseph
    Alstetter, Michael
    Alvarez, Manuel
    Ames, roger
    Amitin, Mark Hall
    Amram, David
    Anapol, Malthon/with President John F. Kennedy, 1960
    Anderson, Genevieve
    Anderson, Marian
    Anderson, Neil and David McLellan guitar duo
    Andrychowsk, Casmera
    Angelone, Albert
    Another Carnival
    Apples in Stereo, The
    Apter, Morris
    Archer, Tasmin
    Armentano, Dominick
    Aronson, Stanley
    Art Ensemble of Chicago
    Ashachau, Jeff
    Ashe, Arthur
    Ashley, Al
    Ashley, Albert J.
    Ashworth, Cynthia
    Asimov, Isaac
    Asimov, Isaac with James Vinson
    Athanson, George
    Aust, Kandyce
    Auten, Arthur
    Authority, The
    Avalon String Quartet
    Averill, Donald
    Aycock, Carol White
  - Ba-Be (Box Ba-Be)
    Babbidge, Homer
    Babbitt, Bruce
    Babel, Felix
    Babel, Felix A.
    Babeneau, Ninette
    Bacall, Lauren
    Bacon, Ethel/portrait
    Bacon, Ethel, in library
    Bacon, Ethel, with Elizabeth Ivey, David Goldenberg, Walter Harrison and others
    Bagg, Ian
    Bagwell, Jeff see separate box
    Baibel
    Bailey, Edson
    Baker, James
    Baker, James H.
    Baker, Vin
    Balmer, John
    Banda, Frederick
    Banis, William
    Banks, Arthur C., Jr.
    Banzhaf, Walter "Wally"
    Barber, Elizabeth
    Barber, Frank
    Barber, Jeanne
    Barbieri, Kim
    Barella, Washington
    Barker-Duncan, Karen
    Barlow, Channing
    Barlow, Claire
    Barnes, Mahlon
    Barnes, Wallace
    Barney faculty/unidentified
    Barney School of Business Deans oversize
    Barney, Austin Dunham II
    Barrett, Karin
    Barstow, Jane
    Bartels, Anna
    Barton, Bruce
    Barton, Christin
    Bar-Tov, Hanoch
    Bartoz, Wally
    Basil, Joseph A.
    Bassong, Lanne
    Bates, Edward
    Battalino, Amelia T.
    Battles, Ford
    Baudin, Barbara
    Bauer, Harold see also Bauer collection
    Beach Boys
    Beach, Harry
    Beach, Morrison H.
    Bear, Dorothy
    Beck, Ann
    Begue, Mrs. Claude
    Behl, Wolfgang
    Belkin, Richard
    Bell, David
    Bellmay, Arlene
    Bellmay, Judson
    Bennet, Collin B.
    Bennet, James
    Bennett, Marlene and John with Michael Yaffee
    Benny, Jack/sketch
    Bensall, Robin
    Bent, James
    Ben-Zion, Orgad
    Berger, Ron
    Bergin, Edward
    Bergner, Carl
    Berkman, Samuel
    Berkman family
    Bernaiche, Jennifer
    Bernstein, Carl
    Bernstein, George
    Berons, grace
    Berrigan, Philip
    Berry, Kenneth
    Bershtein, Edward
    Berson, Selwyn
    Berton, Lee
    Berual, Victoria
    Besmich, Martin
    Bethea, Robert
    Bethune, Anthony
    Between the Lines
  - Bi-Bris (Box Bi-Bris)
    Biegler, John c.
    Big Twist and the Mellon Fellows
    Bikel, Theodore
    Bishop, Adelaide
    Biskupiak, Brian
    Bissell, Richard
    Bissell, Richard H., Jr.
    Black, Robert
    Blackman, Neal
    Blameless
    Blanshan, Sue
    Blauers, Robyn
    Bleiberg, Robert
    Bliss, Ruth
    Block, Robert
    Blodolay, Laurdella
    Blomstrann, Robert/Eight Year Man, adult student, newspaper article
    Blood, Curt
    Bloom, claire
    Bloomfield, Francis
    Bloomfield, Frank and dean H. Shively
    Blue Meanies
    Blumenfeld, Joseph
    Boak
    Boaz, Sharon
    Bodolay, laurdella
    Bolcolm, William
    Boles, Barbara
    Bonaca, Jeanne R.
    Bonacini and Carousova/trio
    Bonacini, Renato
    Bond, Julian
    Bonocini, Renato
    Bonsall, Robin
    Boonshaft, Peter
    Boonshaft, Peter Loel
    Born, Walter
    Boston, Chester
    Botowta, Jennifer
    Bottle Rockets, The
    Boutelle, Sara Holmes
    Bova, Ben
    Bowmaster, Terry
    Boyer, Peter
    Boykin, Phillip
    Boyle, Michael
    Boyton, rick
    Braceland, Francis
    Bradamas, John
    Bradbury, Evelyn
    Bradbury, Evelyn Mae
    Brademas, John
    Bradley, Ed
    Braher, Richard
    Brant, Henry
    Braunthal, Gerard
    Brayfield, Bill
    Brazeau, Paul
    Breit, Peter
    Bremer, Richard
    Brenna, Thomas
    Brennan, Thomas
    Briscoe, Mrs. John
    Briscoe, Mrs. John d.
    Bristal, Curtis
  - Brit-Ce (Box Brit-Ce)
    Britton, Michael
    Brockman, Jane
    Brockway, Weston
    Broden, Barry
    Brokaw, Tom
    Bromley, David
    Bromley, Robert
    Brotherhood, John O., Jr.
    Brown, Alice Cooke
    Brown, James R.
    Brown, Linda
    Brown, Richard
    Brown, Steve
    Brown, Stillman
    Brown, William
    Brownell, Samuel
    Bruce, Duane
    Bruttomesso, Raymond
    Bryant, Roger
    Buckberrough, Sherry
    Buckles, Joseph
    Buckley, William f.
    Buckner, Herbert, editor of
    Budd, Edward
    Budds, William
    Budds, William E.
    Budnes, Mrs.
    Budney, Mrs.
    Budries, David
    Bugl, Paul
    buhle
    Bullock, James
    Buonocore, Gloria
    Burg, Louise
    Burger, Elizabeth
    Burn, North
    Burns, George
    Busemeyer, Stephen
    Bush, Esther
    Butterfield, Victor
    Cacenes, Joe
    Calder, Alexander
    Caldicott, Helen
    Calhoun, Jose
    Callazo, Charles
    Calmer, Robert
    Caluda, Cherie
    Cam p, J. Holden
    Campbell Jared
    Canedy, Charles
    Canham, Erwin, editor of Christian Science Monitor
    Cannon, John
    Capen, Elizabeth
    Caravant, David
    Carey, Ellen
    Carl, Robert
    Carlson, Judy
    Carlson, Margaret
    Carlson, Pauline
    Carrerns, Marcos
    Carsky, Mary
    Carson, John
    Carter, Jimmy
    Caruso, David
    Caruso, Josephine
    Case, Kristie
    Case professors
    Cassidy, Jane
    Castro, Luiz deMaura
    Cawley, John
    Celmer, Robert
  - Ch-Cl (Box Ch-Cl)
    Chang, Mrs. Wilson/head cataloger, library
    Chapin/portrait unveiling
    Chapman, Frank
    Chase, David
    Cheney, Timothy
    Cheney, William Fitch
    Chernack, Bob
    Chester, Herbert
    Chiarenza, Frank
    Chidress, Alice
    Chiffons, The
    Childress, Alice
    Childs, Samuel
    Chilnick, Judy
    Chinitz, Benjamin
    Christensen, Caryn
    Chuck
    Chupka, Lee
    Chupka, Lee Ann
    Chute, Charolyn
    Citron, Cynthia
    Clark, Elizabeth W.
    Clark, Kaye
    Clark, Lenard
    Clark, Paul
    Clark, Raymond
    Clark, Richard
    Clarke, Mr.
    Clarke, Susan Slater
    Clarks, The
    Cleaver, Eldridge
    Clement, Charles
    Clemmons, Jackson
    Clemow, Bice
    Clewell, Dayton
    Clous, Sanford
  - Co-Cu (Box Co-Cu)
    Coasters
    Cobb, Jewell Plummer
    Coffey, Richard
    Coffin, Donald
    Coffin, Mrs.
    Coffin, Vincent
    Coffin, Vincent with Trachtenberg and Woodruff/ 3 presidents
    Coffin, Vincent/with adjunct faculty
    Coganello, Robert
    Cogswell, Robert and Joseph Ladone
    Cohen, Emma and Maurice/event with others
    Cohen, Martin
    Cohn, Richard
    Cokkinias, Peter
    Colarulli, Chuck
    Cole, Abioseh and Widener, Larry
    Cole, Mr.
    Coleman, Ornette
    Coleman, Winifred (president of St. Joseph College)
    Colen, Richard
    Coles, Connie
    Coles, Robert
    Collazzo, Charles
    Collier, Christopher
    Colliner, Marilyn
    Collins, Atwood
    Collins, Joyce
    Collins, Marva
    Collins, Robert
    Colliver, marilyn
    Colony
    Collura
    Colvocoressef, Harvey
    Comeau, Mr.
    Condon, Charles
    Congleton, Peter
    Connecticut Dance Theater
    Connors, Mary Ann
    Conrad, Arthur
    Conrad, Donald
    Cook, C. Donald
    Cook, Charles B.
    Cook, Hale H. and Margit Mortensson
    Cook, Tina
    Coolbrith, Allison
    Coombs, Richard
    Cooper, Irma
    Copes, Paul
    Copland, Aaron
    Correale, Pete
    Corruli
    Costello, Ann
    Coster, Doris
    Coster, Luiz De Moura
    Costikyan, Kevork
    Cote, Dick
    Courtwright, David
    Cowles, W. Sheffield
    Craft, David
    Craig, Gary and Jack Elliot
    Crelan, John
    Crimmins, Barry
    Crolius, William and Janers Chirizl?
    Crook, Katherine
    Cross, Gordon
    Cross, Richard
    crothen
    Crystal, Billy
    Cullen, David
    Culpeper, grant
  - D (Box D)
    D'Lugin, Victor
    Daddario, Emilio
    Dalin, David
    Daniels, Marta
    Danielson, J. David
    Darian, Ron+
    Darrow, Daniel
    David, George
    Davis, Anthony
    Davis, Daniel
    Davis, Donald
    Davis, James
    Davis, John M.K.
    Davis, Lynne
    Davis, Vernal
    Davis, Zima
    Davison, Bart
    Day, Victoria
    Dearle, Dorothy
    DeCazio, Mchael
    DeChiara, Al
    Decker, Robert
    Deiessteri, Norman
    Del Glorno, Bette
    Del Vikings, The
    Delle-Vegni, Oquiles
    Dello Joeo, Norman
    Demarco, Rick '75 with cat
    DeMare, Ahthony
    Demers, David
    Demgen, Julie
    Dempsey, john
    Den Ouden, Bernard
    Derick, Martha and sister, former residents of Bates house?
    DeRusha, Stanley
    Dervish
    Desmond, Roger
    Deyo, Donald
    Diabelli String Quartet
    Diard, William and Aliani, Gloria
    Diaspora Yeshiva Band
    Dickinson, Mrs. E. B.
    Diemente
    Diemente, Edward
    Dilian, Frances
    Dillon, John
    Dissidenten
    Dix, Douglas
    Dodd, Christopher
    Dodd, Thomas
    Dole, Bob
    Dollshead
    Donahue, Thomas
    Downes, Edmund
    Downey, John
    Doyle, Donald
    Doyle, Joseph
    Draganescu, Ovidui with Angla Hognoj, anna Smolka, and Kryzysztof Roszkowski
    Drew-Bear, Robert
    Driscoll, John
    Druckman, Jacob
    duBois, Ellen
    Duda, Kevin
    Dudley, Ernest
    Duffey, Joseph
    Duffie, Thomas M.
    Dulz, Ms.
    Dumond, Arnaud
    Duncan, J. C.
    Dunsmore, Barrie
    durall, rob
    Duzak, Edward
    Dwight, Charles T.
    Dyckman, John
    Dyer, Alice
  - E-Fig (Box E-Fig)
    Easterbrook, Jonathan
    Eaton, Howard
    Eaves, Howard Whitley
    Ebel, Harry
    Ebel, Henry
    Eddy, Deborah
    Edmonds and Curley
    Eggen, Alfred
    Ehrbright, Lee
    Eichar, Douglas
    Eidler, Nestor
    Eisdorfer, Carl
    Eisenhower, Dwight
    Ellis, Donald
    Ellis, Herb
    Ellis, Willaim
    Ellsworth
    Ellsworth, Grace and Harris, Donald
    Ellsworth, Grace.
    Elmer, Edward
    Emerson String Quartet
    Emmons, Shirlee
    Employee Awards
    Enders, John
    Enders, Ostrom
    Engelberger, Joseph
    English, James
    Ensign, R.
    Ensling, Paul
    Epstein, Alvin
    Erickson, Florence
    Erickson, Norman
    Ericson, Richard
    Estarellas, Juan
    Etherington, Edwin
    Eubanks, Phil
    Eubanks, Phillip
    Evans, Roland (with Bob Novak)
    Evica, George Michael
    Exile
    Fabulon
    Faculty Group in auditorium? 1990s
    Fagan, Nina Paranov
    Fahey, Mary B.
    Fairfield-Sonn, Michael
    Falvey, Marcella
    Farberman, Harold
    Farkas, Alexander
    Farley, William
    Farrelly, Alexander
    Farris
    Fat
    Faux, Victor
    Feierabend, John
    Feierabend, Lillie
    Feldman, Amy
    Feldman, Jeff
    Feldman, Rabbi Abraham
    Ferguson, Maynard
    Ferreber, Sallie
    Feshback, Sidney
    Fidlar, Dorothy
    Fiereband, John
    Fighting Gravity
  - Fil-Gard (Box Fil-Gard)
    Filer, John
    Finch, Margaret
    Fine, James
    Finley, C. David
    Finn, Jim
    Firkusny, Rudolf
    Fischer, Annie
    Fitzgerald, Sue
    Fitzmaurice, Anne
    Fitzurka, Robert
    Flaherty, William
    Fleming, Arthur, United States Surgeon General
    Foberg, Ann
    Fogg, Rosemary
    Folklorico
    Follow for Now
    Forbes, Malcolm
    Forbes, Malcom S., Jr.
    Forde, Sandra
    Forrester, Robert
    Foster, Raymond
    Foster, Richard
    Foster, Serron
    Fountain, Melissa
    Fournier, Amy with Karina Martin, Michelle McKenzie and Keila Huelle/women's soccer alumni, class of 1995
    Fowle, Frank, III
    Francis, Margaret
    Frank, Claude
    Frankenthaler, Helen
    Freed
    Freund, Richard
    Freundlick, Larry
    Frey, Mary
    Friedlander. Bernard
    Friedman, Edward
    Fritz, Amy
    Froelich, John
    Frosh, Keevan
    Fruxal, G.
    Fryer, Atherton
    Fulco, Dominic
    Fuller
    Fuller, Alfred
    Fuller, Mary Primrose
    Fuller, Primrose
    Fussel, Mr.
    Gaines, Edythe
    Gaines, Reg E.
    Gainsbourg, Serge
    Gaitor, Woodrow Wilson
    Gal, Ehud
    Galbraith, John Kenneth
    Galdeans, the
    Gall, Ferenz
    Gallagher, Tess
    Galliano
    Galvin, John
    Garbousova, raya
    Gardow, Ernest
    Gardow, Margorie with Farideh Ighani and Monirollah Ighani
  - Garu-Go (Box Garu-Go)
    Gaurich, Larry
    Garuer
    Gaver, Harold
    Gayle, Crystal
    Geber, Stephen
    Gehman, Chester
    Geiger, Jack
    Geist, Patricia
    Gendrochi, Tom
    Gengras, Elizabeth
    Gentlemen of Jazz, featuring Ramsey Lewis
    Gerasimov, Gennady
    Gerson, Noel
    Ghasassia, Jill
    Ghiglia, Oscar
    Giamatti, Bartlett
    Giannanaros, Demetrios
    Giannaros, Demetrios
    Gibbs, Elizabeth
    Gibbs, Lois
    Gibson, Raymond
    Gilbert, Paul
    Gilder, George
    Gill, Brendan
    Gillespie, Dizzy
    Giorgio, p. Anthony
    Giorgio, P. Anthony
    Giorgio, Pl Anthony
    Giovanni, Nikki
    Gittle, Stella
    Glasson, Lloyd
    Glover, Milton
    Glover, Robert
    Glover, William
    Glyden, Kelly
    God Street Wine
    Goff, C. N.
    Gol, Ehud
    Goldbaum, Jesse
    Goldberg, William
    Goldberg, William I.
    Goldenberg, David
    Goldfarb
    Goldfield, Claire
    Goldick, Howard
    Goldschmidt, Bernhard
    Goldspiel-Provost
    Goldstein, Melvin
    Goldstein, William
    Goleman, Daniel
    Goodman, Benny with Donald Harris, Christopher Dellauso, Alexander Lepak, Manuel Alvarez
    Goodwin, Dorothy
    Gordon, Mildred
    Gordon, Mildred Koburn
    Gordon, Ted
    Gore, Albert Sr.
    Gorky's Zygotic Mynci
    Gould, George
    Gould, Laurence
    Goyette, James F.
  - Gr-Harp (Box Gr-Harp)
    Graduate Percussion Quartet: Gene koshinski, Murray Most, Neeraj Mehta, Tim Broscious
    Grames, Linda
    Grandpre, Raoul
    Grant, Thomas
    Grasso, Ella
    Grauel, John Stanley with martin mantis, Jamie Selzer and Debra Schnier
    Gray, Edward
    Gray, Francince du Plessix
    Gray, Harry and Helen
    Gray, Harry Jack
    Gray, John
    Gray, kevin
    Gray, Walter
    Greeman, Richard
    Green, Clifford
    Green, Florence
    Greenberg
    Greenberg, Arnold
    Greenberg, Phyllis
    Greene, Florence
    Greenman, Norman
    Gregorian, Vartan
    Gregory, Dick
    Grella, frank
    Grenon, Russell
    Greza?
    Griffin, William
    Griffin, William and Amelia Battalino
    Griffin, William and Bruce Loessin
    Griffith, Thomas J.
    Griswold, Renwick
    Griswold, Renwick "Wick"
    Grodski, Rabbi Yosef
    Grogory, Dick
    Groomes, Andrea
    Groth, Richard
    Groups see Group box
    Groups/Bowling League
    Groups/Enhp
    Groups/Fuss & O'Neill
    Groups/Past chairman of board
    Groups/regents?
    Groups/unidentified
    Gruber, H
    Gryč, Stephen
    Guardo, Carol
    Gurney, George
    Guru
    Gustarso, Doris
    Guttmacher, Alan
    Gwynn, Robert
    Haas, Ruth
    Haase, Walter
    Haase, Walter Hennessey, Edward L., Jr.
    Hackerman, Norman
    Hadad, Alan
    Haffstrom, William
    Hagel, Raymond
    Haggerty, Kristen
    Hale, Donald
    Hale, Virginia
    Haley, Alex
    Hall, Rich
    Hall, Warren
    Hamel, Albert
    Hamel, Molley Kalogeros
    Hamilton, T. Stewart
    Hamilton-Collins, Joyce
    Hammer, Al
    Han, Wu
    Hanson, Bernard
    Hanson, Raymond
    Hardesty, Monica
    Harman, Risa Renae
    Harper, Valerie
    Harper, Valerie with Mayor Mike Peters and Ronald E. Compton
    Harris
    Harris, Donald
    Harris, Howard
    Harris, Reese
    Harrison, Larry
    Harrison, Walt
    Harrison, Walter/at reception
    Harrison, Walter/see also oversize photos for panels from Walt's Wall, 2010
    Harrison, Walter/with students, including America's East basketball game
    Harrison, Walter/with students, including Hillel
    Hart, Gary
    Hart, Ralph
    Hartford Parner Scholarship recipients, 1989
    Hartigan, William
    Hartt College Madrigal Singers
    Hartt/Faculty/Groups
    Hartt, Ralph?
    Harvey, Raymond
  - Harr-Hep (Box Harr-Hep)
    Harrison, Walter and Diane, see box 6
    Haskell, Richard
    Hassell, Arthur
    Haugh, Helen
    Hausen, Herbert
    Hautzig, Walter
    Hawkins, Sherman
    Haynes, James
    Haynes, Lowell
    Headswim
    Heaney, Seamus
    Hegenberger, William
    Heiller, Anton
    Heller, Joseph
    Heller, Josepph
    Hemond, Conrad
    Henderson, Robert
    Hennessey, Edward L, Jr.
    Hepburn, Katharine
    Hepburn, Katharine (at University?)
    Heperan, Harold
  - Her-Hu (Box Her-Hu)
    Herder, John
    Herman, Charles
    Herrmann, Arthur
    Hess, Beth
    Hessen, Robert
    Higby, Wayne and Ryoungia Kim
    Higgs, David
    Hill, Roberta Antamian
    Hillyer, Charles Tudor (portrait unveiling)
    Hincks, Marcia
    Hirschfeld, Al
    Hirschfeld, Al/cartoon of self
    Hirschfeld, Alvin
    Hite, Schera
    Hoff, Diane and Nicole
    Hoffman, Mr. and Mrs. with Humphrey Tonkin
    Hoffman, Roald
    Hoffman, Ronald
    Hoffman, Stanley H.
    Hogan, Marsha
    Hogue, Jason
    Hokanson, William
    Holder, Frederick
    Holloway, James
    Holtz, John
    Honorary degrees recipients
    Hooker, William
    Hoover, David
    Hopkins, Robert
    Horner, Matina
    Horton, Chris
    Horvath, Jane
    Hovery, Daniel
    Howard, Karen
    Howe, Harold II
    Howie the Hawk
    Hubbard, Helen
    Hudnall, Margaret
    Huffman, Kristin
    Hulme, Tony
    Hulusa, Carl
    Huntman, Deborah
    Hurt, H. Thomas
  - I-Keller (Box I-Keller)
    Ianoli, Joseph J., Jr.
    Ictus Vigor
    Ilg, Donald
    Ilumonka, Abi
    Individuals/miscellaneous (some labeled)
    Innes-Brown, Elizabeth
    Ireland, Marin and first acting class
    Ivey, Elizabeth
    Ivry, David
    Jackson, Douglas
    Jackson, Doug and Contemporary Players
    Jackson, Morris/Upward Bound student
    Jacobs, James
    Jacobs, Jim
    Jacobson, Wolimer
    Jacoby, Benjamin
    Jainsen, Wilson
    Jarvis, Mrs. Howard
    Jassem, Harvey
    Jeffrey, W. Stephen
    Jehenson, Yvonne
    Jenoure, Frederick, Jr.
    Jensen, Gordon
    Jerky Boys, The
    Jochum, Veronica
    Johanson, Donald
    Johnson, Kenitra
    Johnson, M. F.
    Johnson, Nancy
    Johnston, Jill
    Jolene
    Jones, Allison
    Jones, Clifford
    Jones, Eleta
    Jones, kathryn
    Jones, Myron
    Jorgensen, Bruce
    Josephs, Denereaux
    Jump in the Water
    Kagan, Joel
    Kahn, Irene see also Kahn Collection and Paranov Collection
    Kahn, Michael with Harvey Resnick
    Kaiser, Philip
    Kalamajka, James
    Kalb, Marvin
    Kaman, Charles
    Kaplan, Ben
    Karas, Jose
    Karl, Robert
    Karr, Gary
    Karsh, Yousef
    Kasevich, Raymond
    Katz, Phyllis
    Kaufman, George
    Kay, Richard
    Kaye, Babbye
    Kearns, Charles M., Jr.
    Keener, James
    Keener, Jim
    Keller, Dick
    Keller, George
    Keller, Mrs. Richard and Mrs. Sidney with Dr. Smith
    Keller, Richard
    Keller, Stephen
  - Kelley-Kut (Box Kelley-Kut)
    Kelley, Ed W.
    Kelley, George
    Kelly, Lynn
    Kelsey, John
    Kelton, Beverly
    Kemp, Jack
    Kemuri
    Kennedy, Robert F.,Jr. at convocation
    Kennedy, X, J.
    Kennelly, Barbara
    Kerby-Miller, Wilma
    Keshwarz, Mohammed
    Killray, Syrus (Lyrus?)
    Kilpatrick, Robert
    Kim, Dorothy Bear
    Kim, Tai Soo
    Kimbrell, Will
    Kimering, John
    King, Coretta Scott
    King, Thom
    Kinsella, Doris
    Kinois, John
    Kirkpatrick, David
    Kirkpatrick, John
    Kissinger, Henry
    Klaber, Michael
    Klarsfeld, Beate
    Klein, Robert
    Kleman, George
    Klock, Nancy
    Klonoski, Ed
    Kloten, Edgar
    Knapp, Elaine
    Knapp, Sherman
    Knauft, Burt
    Knauft, Ruth
    Knauss, Walter P.
    Knepler, Abraham
    Knott, Kenneth
    Knox. Robert c., Jr.
    Koch, Raymond
    Kohn, Mrs. Bernhard
    Kolluri, Bharat
    Komisar, David
    Komisar, John
    Koopman, Georgette
    Koscis, Susan
    Kouatly, Youssef
    Kraemer, ?
    Krall, Walter
    Krasner, Mike
    Krasner, Steve
    Krass, Julie
    Krisst, Raymond
    Kristopik, John
    Kroll, William
    Kubasiewicz, Jan
    Kubik, Franz
    Kuckro, Lee and Anne
    Kudner, Warren Eugene
    Kumin, Maxine
    Kuntz, Paul
    Kuralt, Charles
    Kuszpa, Frank
    Kutik, Ronald
  - L-Log (Box L-Log)
    L A Style
    La Fontaine, Herman
    LaBau, David
    LaBau, David with Richard Custer and Edward Stockton
    Ladd, Everett Carll
    Lafontaine, Hernan
    Lahey, Frank
    Laioe, F.
    Lamming, George
    Lamos, Mark
    Landers, Ann
    Landesburg, Steve
    Lane, Calvin
    Lane, William
    Lang, Donald
    Lange, Jessica
    Lange, Roland
    Lanis, Jen
    Larrabee, Neil
    Larsen, Henry
    Larson, Henry
    Larson, John
    LaSalle, Donald
    Lasbury, Mrs. Ralph C., Jr.
    Lashgari, Malek
    Laub, Dori
    Lawley, Raymond
    Lawson, Jonathan
    Lazarek, William
    Lazear, Robert
    Lazor, John
    Leary, Timothy
    Lebed, Hartzel